法属波利尼西亚
哥 斯 拉
南太平洋
乌克兰
15公里
切尔诺贝利
切尔诺贝利　乌克兰
该死,"许可"用俄语怎么说?
Damn! How do you say "permit"?
我有许可证
I have a permit.
尼克·泰普多普勒斯博士?
Dr. Niko Tapodopolis?
是泰特普勒斯
It's Tatopoulos.
凯尔·泰瑞特,美国国务院派来的
Kyle Terrington. I'm with the U.S. State Department.
他们在干什么?
What are they doing?
你被调职了
You're being reassigned.
但我在这里的工作还没结束
But my work here isn't finished.
现在就结束了
It is now.
帕皮提　塔希提岛
长官,美国方面在施压
Sir. There's pressure from the Americans.
你告诉了他们什么?
What have you told them?
什么都没说
Nothing yet.
有生还者吗?
Are there any survivors?
就一个,长官
Only one, sir.
他很幸运
He was lucky.
让他们出去一下
Get them out.
好的
Sure.
问他发生了什么事
Ask him what happened.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
你看见了什么?老头
What did you see, old man?
ゴジラ
Godzilla.
圣米格尔湾　巴拿马
确定完成
That's affirmative.
嘿
Hey,
你要把我的东西拿到哪去?
where are you going with my stuff?
你好
Hello.
嘿
Hey.
喂
Hello.
喂,那些都是很易碎的
Hello. That's very delicate.
谢谢
Thank you.
尼克·泰普多普勒斯博士
Dr. Niko Topodopeless?
是泰特普勒斯
Tatopoulos.
管他呢,快点,让这些人离开码头
Whatever. Come on, get these people off of the pier!
抱歉,长官,能告诉我来这里要干嘛?
Excuse me. Sir, what am I doing here?
小心走路,不要随便和人说话
Watch your step. Don't talk to anybody.
快点,叫他们离开码头!
Come on, get them off the damn pier!
这里怎么回事?有泄漏吗?
What is all this, some kind of spill?
对,差不多
Yea. Something like that.
瞧,我为核能管理委员会工作
Look, I work for the Nuclear Regulatory Commission...
但意外事故和泄漏和我无关
but accidents and spills aren't my field.
我们知道
We know.
你知道你中断了我研究切尔诺贝利蚯蚓已经3年的工作了吗?
You know you've interrupted a 3-year study of the Chernobyl earthworm?
对,你是蚯蚓人,对吗?
Yeah, you're the worm guy, right?
那个地区的辐射污染
The radioactive contamination in that area,
导致了蚯蚓的基因突变
has mutated the earthworm's DNA.
你知道那意味什么吗?
You know what that means?
我有种感觉要找到答案了
I got a feeling I'm about to find out.
这意味着,因为人为的事故
It means, because of a man-made accident,
使得切尔诺贝利的蚯蚓体积增加了17%
the Chernobyl earthworms are now 17% larger than they were before.
17%?听起来很大
Seventeen percent? Sounds pretty big.
它们非常巨大
They're enormous.
这就证明我是一名生物学家
That's what I'm trying to saying I'm a biologist.
我采取放射物标本然后研究他们
I take radioactive samples and I study them.
太好了,这就是标本,研究吧
That's great. Here's your sample. Study it.
什么标本?
What sample?
你正站在上面
You're standing in it.
我没看到
I don't see it.
在哪?
Where is it?
我没看到
I don't see it.
上校!上校!
Colonel! Colonel!
那是一个脚印!
That was a footprint!
我站在一个脚印里面!
I was standing inside of a footprint!
没错
That's right.
但...
But...
世界上还没有什么动物能有这么大的脚印
there's no animal in the world that makes footprints like that.
有吗?
Is there?
我告诉过他们这不是你的专长
I told them this is not your field,
但他们从不听天才的话
but they never listen to genius.
这位是埃尔希·查普曼,国家古生物研究所的
This is Elsie Chapman, of the National Institute of Palaeontology.
她是你的上司
She's your boss.
这些是脚印,对吗?
Those were footprints, right?
是的,没错
Yes, they were.
有人看见是什么东西干的吗?
Did anybody see what made them?
事实上
Actually,
还没人运气这么好
no such luck.
事件发生的很快,直到结束后才有人发现
It happened so fast, nobody knew what hit them until it was over.
埃尔希
Elsie.
什么事?
Yeah?
带子来了,法国终于愿意公开了
The tape's in. The French finally released it.
对,这是一艘日本罐头厂的船
Yea. This is a Japanese cannery ship,
在法属波利尼西亚附近沉没
that was attacked and sunk near French Polynesia.
我们认为是有关连的
We believe it's connected.
顺便说一下,克莱文博士,见过这位蚯蚓人了吗?
By the way, Dr. Craven, have you met the worm guy?
对不起,热伤风
Sorry. Summer cold.
嘿,快点!快点!行吗?
Hey. Come on, Come on, all right?
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
等等!等等!等等!
Wait, wait, wait!
他们说整个礼拜都会下雨
They say it'll rain all week.
这些袋子是怎么回事?
What's with the bags?
凯曼的杂货
Caiman's groceries.
哦,天啊
Oh, girl.
说说就见鬼了
Speak of the devil.
什么?
What?
这个就是个残疾版本
This one is the midget version.
这个让我看起来像是试图专业一点的
And this one makes me look like a trying professional.
把它排在五点,行吗?
Can we put this on the 5, please?
你觉得我该不该问问他?
You think I should ask him?
不要!
No.
我要问他
I'm gonna ask him.
不要
No!
我要
I will.
奥黛莉
Audrey.
你和克里斯谈过吗?
Did you talk with Humphries?
这里谈不合适
This is not the place.
只要告诉我,有和他谈过了吗?
Just tell me. Did you talk with him?
那是你跟罗杰古斯之间的事
It's between you and Rodriguez.
你说真的吗?他会考虑让我去工作吗?
You serious? He's gonna consider me for the job?
他说了什么?
What else did he say?
我们何不晚饭后再谈?
Why don't we talk about it over dinner tonight?
在你家
Your place.
凯曼先生,你已经结婚了
Mr. Caiman, you're married.
对,但你很漂亮
Yes, and you're very beautiful.
我之前没有告诉过你吗?
Have I ever told you that before?
凯曼先生!
Mr. Caiman!
三年来我连下班后和周末都在为你做工作
I've been doing research for you after hours and weekends for over three years.
这工作对我来说太重要了
This is a very important job to me.
作为您的助手我年龄已经过大了
I'm too old to be your assistant anymore.
我需要自己的事业有发展的空间
I need to know this job is going someplace.
那今晚和我共进晚餐
So have dinner with me tonight.
我不能
I can't.
这是你自己的选择
It's your choice.
好了,我们走
Okay, let's go.
查理,见过你的新助手狄丝瑞·庞小姐
Charlie. Say hello to your new co-anchor, Ms. Desiree Pon.
你好,狄丝瑞,欢迎加盟
Hello, Desiree, welcome aboard.
马克
Mark,
能给我一个枕头、电话簿或什么的吗?
Can I have a pillow, phone book, something?
...三...二...
...Three, two...
纽约市民们好,今天下午五点
Hello, New York. Today at 5,
我会问胖帕特,雨什么时候停止
we'll ask Fat Pat when the rain will end.
大佩德罗角角　牙买加
那么
So,
你3年都在切尔诺贝利挖蚯蚓?是吗?
three years digging up worms in Chernobyl? Was it?
那泰塔普勒斯太太怎么办?
How did Mrs. Tatapolis handle it?
是泰特普勒斯,我还没有结婚
It's the Tatopoulos. I'm actually not married.
真的?
Really?
那女朋友或是...?
A girlfriend, or...?
哦,没有
Uh...No.
也许我太投入于工作了
Perhaps I work too much.
那么...
So...
你意思是目前还没有什么人...
Do you mean to tell me there's no one who holds a...
在你心中拥有特殊地位?
special place in your heart?
没有,很久都没有了
No. Not for a long time now.
或许你并不适合这次的工作
Well, you may be the wrong man for the job,
但我觉得你很可爱
but I think you're cute.
谢谢
Thank you.
她觉得我很可爱
She thinks I'm cute.
他们是什么人?
Who the hell are they?
军士,把这些人弄走
Sergeant, Get those people out of there.
他们是我的人
They're with me.
是吗?
Is that right?
你是谁?
Who are you?
拉罗谢尔人财保险公司
La Rochelle Casualty and Property Insurance.
我们正在做定损报告
We're preparing our report.
你们还真是神速
You're pretty damn fast.
那是我们的工作
That's our job.
但你的人妨碍到我们工作了
Your people are getting in the way of my job.
上校,你认为这是什么东西造成的?
Colonel, what do you think could have done this?
听好,罗奇先生
Listen, Mr. Roach,
带你的人离开这里,否则我要赶人了
you get your people out of here, or I will.
东部海岸　美利坚合众国
船长喝完咖啡
The captain's getting some coffee.
然后就会来教训你
Then he's gonna kick your asses.
那个傻瓜到底在做什么?
What the hell is that dope-head doing?
阿蒂
Artie,
怎么搞的?我们为什么会慢下来?
what the hell's wrong? Why are we slowing down?
我不知道,船开足马力的
I don't know, she's at full throttle.
也许是网到了什么重的东西
Maybe she's heavy in the net.
呦,我们怎么停下来了?满网了吗?
Yo. How come we stopped? Nets full?
我感觉不像
I don't think so.
我们肯定绊到了什么东西
We must be caught on something.
把网收起来,把它拉上来!拉回来
Bring in the nets. Bring them up! Pull them in now.
出了什么事?
What's going on?
我们在收网
We're bringing them in.
发动机温度太高了,我应该关掉吗?
Let the engines heating up. Should I shut them down?
不,继续拉
No, keep pulling.
我正在努力!我正在努力!
I'm trying! I'm trying!
切断绳子!切断绳子!把网切断!
Cut them loose! Cut them loose! Cut them net!
小心!
Look out!
切断网绳!
Cut them loose now!
快!快!
Hurry! Hurry!
- 船要沉了 - 放掉网!放掉网!
- She's going down! - Let it go! Let it go!
听见了吗?
Do you hear that?
上校,抱歉打扰,长官
Colonel. Excuse me, sir.
我们刚刚接到报告,三条鱼船沉没了
We just got a report of three fishing trawlers going down.
你认为和这件事有关联?
What makes you think it's related?
船是被拉下去的,长官
The trawlers were pulled under, sir.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
那里离东海岸不到200公里
It's only 200 miles off the Eastern seaboard,
我们却不知道那是什么东西
and we don't even know what it is.
兽脚类恐龙
Theropoda allosaurus.
什么?
What?
我们曾认为某些类型的巨大爬行动物死在了白垩纪时期
Some type of enormous reptile that we believed died out in the Cretaceous Period.
那他这60亿年一直躲在哪里?
So where's it been hiding the last 60 million years?
如果是和辐射有关呢?
What about the traces of radiation?
有辐射是会不正常的,这就是线索
The radiation isn't an anomaly. It's the clue.
这个动物相比恐龙也更加巨大
This animal is much too big to be some kind of lost dinosaur.
那么别告诉我是怎么回事,告诉我那是什么?
Well. Don't tell me what it isn't, tell me what it is.
看,我们所知道的
Well, what do we know?
它第一次是在...
It was first sighted...
法属波利尼西亚被发现的,对吧?
off of the French Polynesian Pacific. Right?
那地区已被曝光进行了几十次核试验
That area has been exposed to dozens of nuclear tests.
嗯哼,因此有了辐射
Uh-huh. Hence the radiation.
不,不只这样
No. More than that.
我认为那是一个突变品种
I believe it's a mutated aberration.
和岛上的辐射余波混杂出的结果
A hybrid caused by the fallout on these islands.
和你的蚯蚓一样吗?
Like your earthworms?
对,对
Yes. Yes.
我们在找一个前所未有的生物
We're looking at a completely incipient creature.
一个新的物种
The dawn of a new species.
一个物种诞生者
The first of its kind.
纽约
费城
不夜之城
我的生活糟透了
My life sucks.
噢,少来了
Oh, please.
你的生活不糟
Your life doesn't suck.
他的才糟
His life sucks.
因为我娶了你
Because I'm married to you.
我真不敢相信他置我不理了
I cannot believe he put the moves on me.
我给他做了这么多事情
After everything I've done for him.
他是个浑蛋
He is scum.
对他来说,你就像一对乳房一样在说话
As far as he consumed, you're just a pair of breasts that talk.
嘿,真有想象力
Hey, there's an image.
我告诉你,他很下流
I'm telling you, he is dirt.
他是恶棍,臭水沟里只有狗会吃的垃圾
He's a douche-bag, gutter-slime' dog-crap puke-chunks.
嘿嘿,我在吃东西,没看见我在吃东西吗?
Hey, hey. I'm eating, you don't see I'm eating?
奥黛莉,你心地太善良了
Audrey, you're too damn nice.
这就是你的问题
That's your problem.
心善让你在这个城市一无所有
Nice gets you nothing in this town.
在是狗咬狗的社会
It's dog-eat-dog.
你要成为一个杀手把对手除掉
You gotta be a killer to get ahead.
明白我的意思吗?
You what I am saying?
对不起,亲爱的,但...
I'm sorry, baby, but...
你真的没有那样的能力
you just don't got what it takes.
你不是这么认为的吧?是吗?野兽
You dont't think that's true? Do you. Animal?
不,太正确了,你是个好人
Yea. Pretty much. You're a nice person. You know.
好人最后都没有好报
Nice guys finish last.
只要有需要,我会很强硬的
I can be tough if I want.
是啊,当然
Yeah, sure.
我能
I can.
不,是啊,不
No, yeah, no.
随便了
Whatever.
哦,我的天哪
Oh, my God!
能把音量调高点吗?
Could you turn that up please?
...过去了12个小时,目前情况仍然不明...
...Sometime in the last 12 hours. It is not known yet...
是尼克
It's Nick.
他是谁?
Who is he?
他是我大学时的男朋友
He was my college sweetie.
他在电视上看起来很帅
Wow. He looks so handsome on TV.
坠机现场周围有严密的安全措施...
There is tight security around the crash site...
可能因为机上有保密性的军用物品
possibly due to the sensitive military cargo on the plane.
快点,快点,你要把东西卸下来吗?
Come on, come on, You wanna unload this thing?
我已经湿透了
I'm getting soaked here.
快点,行吗?
Come on, will you?
嘿,乔伊!要去东海岸抓一条小鱼来吗?
Hey, Joe! Gonna catch one of them little fish in the East River?
希望如此
I hope so.
但,你从来都不会知道
But you never know.
我意思是,今天可能是我的幸运日
I mean, today could be my lucky day.
你这样只会感冒
The only thing you'll catch is a cold.
嘿
Hey.
我...我钩上了
I... I got a bite.
老兄,我钩上了!
Boy, do I have a bite!
别让它跑了,乔伊
Don't let up on him, Joe.
你钩到个大条的,亲爱的
You got a big one, baby.
把它控制住
Hold on to it. Now.
你要对决吗?
You want to fight?
他在这里,女士们先生们
Here he is, ladies and gentlemen,
你们一直在等待的这个人
the man you've all been waiting for.
致一个让纽约更安全的人
Yours for a safer New York,
你们的市长,艾伯特市长!
your mayor, Mayor Ebert!
谢谢,谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我要感谢大家的到来
I want to thank you all for coming out,
在纽约这样一个美丽的天气时
on this beautiful New York City day.
四年前,人们不相信我能降低犯罪率
Four years ago, people didn't think that I would reduce crime.
但是我办到了!
But I did!
哦,我的天啊
Oh, my God.
走!我们离开这里!
Move! Let's get out of here!
很高兴我们搬到了新地点
I'm grateful we're getting a new set.
我知道管理层做出了承诺
I know that represents a commitment from management.
但我不明白的是
Here's what I don't understand:
为什么我们是唯一没有报导韩国杂货店抢劫案的电台
Why we're the only station in town that doesn't have the Korean grocery holdup as our lead.
我们的报导是什么?又在下雨了!
I mean, What's our lead? Rain, again!
妈?
Mom?
我知道,参加聚会的人对我们优雅的形象印象深刻
I know, it impresses the people at the parties you go to that we're classy.
抱歉
Sorry,
我才不报道什么国家之间的狗屁战争
I just don't give a rat's ass about a war in some country...
有些言论都是禁止发表的
whose name I can't even pronounce.
真正的报道是什么?
How about a real story?
头儿...
Sir?
我认为你的报导刚刚走过了窗外
I think your story just walked by the window.
什么?
What?
也许我们可以去一下韩国杂货店受害者的病房里
Maybe we can get in the Korean grocer's hospital room.
那么,你的罗密欧叫什么名字?
So did this Romeo have a name?
尼克·泰特普勒斯
Nick Tatopoulos.
天哪,你就因为这名字甩了他吗?
Jesus. Is that why you dumped him?
不是
No.
你们在一起多久了?
How long did you go out for anyway?
大约四年
Nearly four years.
小妞,我很惊讶他居然不向你求婚
Girl, I'm surprised he didn't ask you to marry him.
但,这就是问题所在
Well, that's the problem.
他求过
He did.
告诉我这不是另一场游行
Tell me that's not another parade.
我不认为那是游行
I don't think that's a parade.
稍后请...
Please stand by.
那是什么东西?
What the hell is that?
你们没事吧?没伤到吧?没事吧?
Are you alright? Are you cut? You alright?
维克多,别犯傻
Victor! Don't be stupid.
哦...老天...
Oh... My...
耶稣,玛利亚,约瑟夫!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
这真的是...
That is really...
好大
large.
- 天哪 - 天哪!
- Oh, my God. - Oh, my God!
来吧,你这个混蛋,来吧!
Come on, you bastard. Come on!
哦,天啊
Ah. Jesus.
- 维克多 - 等一下
- Victor, - Wait second.
快回来,你个傻瓜
get back here, you retard!
快来人救命啊!
Somebody do something!
快!快!
Come on! Come on!
能告诉我们是怎么回事吗?
Can you tell us what's going on?
小心
Watch it!
机动部队指挥中心　新泽西
奥尼尔军士报到,长官
Sergeant O'Neal, sir.
市长办公室有指示吗?
Any word from the mayor's office?
是的,长官,他们已经同意疏散城市
Yes, sir. They've agreed to evacuate the city.
他们调用了国民警卫队
They've called the National Guard.
等等,疏散曼哈顿?那里有三百万人口
Wait. Evacuate Manhattan? That's over 3 million people.
以前有这么做过吗?
Has that ever been done before?
我想没有
I don't think so.
他现在在哪里?
Where is he now?
我们...我们失去了跟踪信号,长官
We are... We lost sight of it, sir.
你能再说一遍吗?
You wanna run that by me again?
在...第一次攻击之后,他就...
A... After its initial... attack, he...
消失了
disappeared.
国防部秘书伯克来电
Secretary of Defense Burk is on the line.
我想不通,这么大的东西怎么就消失了?
I don't understand. How can something so big just disappear?
我们不确定,但...
We're not sure, but...
是的,是的,他可能回到河里了
Yeah, yeah. He probably returned to the river.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
我说,瞧瞧这里
I mean, look at it.
多么完善
It's perfect.
一座岛,周围都是水
An island, water on all sides.
世界上在没有其它像这样的岛屿了
But like no other island in the world.
这地方很容易给他藏身
This's a place where he can easily hide.
他就在里面某个地方
He's in there someplace.
12号频道用磁带拍到了
Channel 12 caught it on tape.
大家好,我查尔斯·凯曼
Hello, I'm Charles Caiman,
在WIDF新闻台作报道
in the WIDF news center.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我们纽约人认为自己见多识广
we New Υorkers like to think we've seen it all,
但你接下来看到的会超乎想象到让你震惊
but what you're going to see now will shock you beyond belief.
这段镜头是关于...
This is footage we have that indicates...
一只迷失的恐龙在曼哈顿乱窜
that there is a dinosaur loose in Manhattan.
WIDF这段独家影响摄于半小时之前
WIDF's exclusive footage was shot barely half an hour ago.
WIDF摄影师
WIDF cameraman,
维克多·帕洛蒂,外号"野兽",幸存
Victor "Animal" Palotti, survived.
好大的怪物,野兽,你不害怕吗?
Great stuff, Animal. Weren't you scared?
害怕,我以为露西会杀了我
Yeah, I thought Lucy was gonna kill me.
很对,你这个疯狂的家伙
Damn right, you crazy wop.
好了,大家听好
Okay, people.
我们马上要去新泽西的指挥中心
We have to be completely we loca to the New Jersey station.
但时间紧迫
But the time o'clock rocket.
野兽
Animal.
你和凯曼搭乘直升机,马上
You're riding in the chopper with Caiman.
我们走,要起飞了
Let's go, lift off.
- 快点,大家快点! - 你们没问题吧?
- Come on, eveybady. Come on! - Are you going to be all right?
是的,奥黛莉整晚都会跟我们在一起
Yeah. Audrey's gonna spend the night with us.
酷,三个人,太棒了,我有些累
Cool. A threesome. That's excellent. I'm a little tired.
数十人死亡,数千人受伤
Dozens of people are reported killed, thousands others injured.
整个曼哈顿正在设立民防站
Civil defense stations are being set up throughout Manhattan.
但除此之外
But in addition,
城市、军队和医疗部门
city, military and health officials...
都设立在新泽西州海岸指挥中心...
are setting up a command post on the Jersey shore...
用于预防避难...
in anticipation of an evacuation...
我的包,我的包!
My bag. My bag!
凯曼先生
Mr. Caiman.
凯曼先生,等等
Mr. Caiman, wait.
凯曼先生,我有线索了
Mr. Caiman, I've got a lead.
我在军队里认识个人
I know a guy who's on the inside with the military.
现在不行
Not now.
你知道吗?我可以得到一些内部消息
You don't understand. I can get great inside information.
瞧,现在是大人物去上班的时候,行吗,亲爱的?
Look. This is the moment When the big boys go to Work, okay, honey?
包
The bag.
这真是太疯狂了
This is crazy
快点,快点,我们走
Come on, come on, let's go.
等等
Wait up.
快走
Come on.
等等
Wait up.
快点,小心点
Come on, be careful.
能找一辆出租车吗?
Can we get a cab?
奥黛莉,你在想什么?
Audrey, what are you thinking?
走,走,走!
GO, go, go!
去人行道,立刻!
On the sidewalk, right now!
这是城市官员描述的...
In what city officials are describing...
自世贸中心爆炸案以来最糟糕的破坏行为
as the worst act of destruction since the World Trade Center bombing.
成千上万的人被堵在街上
hundreds of thousands have jammed the streets,
这是这个城市有史以来最大规模的疏散行动
in the largest evacuation in this city's history.
很多人,非常多的人对此表示不满
And many people... Many, many people are not happy about it.
这些不高兴的公民...
Among those unhappy citizens...
是5号大街和麦迪逊大道沿线商店的经理
are the managers of the stores along pricey 5th and Madison Ave.
华纳兄弟和迪斯尼商店被抢劫者抢空了
The Warner Bros. And Disney stores have been cleared out by looters.
街道堵塞
And the streets are jammed.
交通依然水泄不通
Traffic's at a standstill.
事件的发生导致紧急车辆不能进入
Emergency vehicles cannot have access to emergencies that may develop.
城外交通缓慢但川流不息...
And there's a slow but steady stream out of the city...
好像长岛和新泽西此刻就是避难营
as if Long Island or New Jersey were any refuge in this time of crisis.
好吧,这下好了
Fine. This is great.
如果我下令疏散是错误的
If I'm wrong on this evacuation,
他们会把我串起来挂在自由女神像的火炬上
they'll string me up from the Liberty torch.
我们不是说好了大选之后才可以吃甜食吗?
Didn't we agreed we weren't gonna have any sweets until after the election?
别管我,吉英
Back off, Gene.
他们是什么人?
Who the hell are they?
这是一个建筑行业企业代表队
It's a contingent of building oWners and business representatives.
我现在没时间说废话
I don't have time for this nonsense.
他们是竞选捐助者
Campaign contributors.
好了,女士们先生们,我来回答你们的问题
All right. Ladies and gentlemen, I share your concerns.
我会让这个城市尽快恢复正常运作
I want to get this city back in business as soon as possible.
拜托
Please.
拉罗谢尔保险公司
La Rochelle Insurance.
我们在你的城市担保了13%的建筑
We represent nearly 13% of the buildings in your city.
你要考虑我们的情绪和财政支持
You can count on our emotional and financial support.
好,谢谢,谢谢
Well, thank you. Thank you.
你准备怎么做?
What do you plan to do?
- 借过,借过 - 等等,你的证件呢?
- Coming through. Coming through. - Wow. Where's your ID?
怎么了?你不看电视的吗?
What's wrong? Don't you watch TV?
你一定要有记者证
You gotta have press ID.
我有证件,我包里本来有的
I've got ID. I had a badge on my bag.
我不知道这是否是一个好主意,露西
I don't know if this is a good idea. Lucy.
你还说什么啊?都偷来了
What are you talking about? You stole it.
你终于有点开窍了,别成窝囊废
Finally you got a little chutzpah. Don't wimp out.
如果凯曼发现了呢?
What if Caiman finds out?
瞧
Look.
你想想看有个前男友会参与大事件的机率是多少?
How often do you think you'll have an ex-boyfriend inside a major story?
这是一个千载难逢的机会
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
只要你坚持这个事情
If you stick this thing.
你有胶水之类的东西吗?
Have you got any glue or something?
抱歉,我把伪造工具留在办公室了
I'm sorry, I left my forgery kit back at the office.
没有牛角面包?
No croissant?
没有,长官
No, monsieur.
哦...你说这就是咖啡?
Oh... You call this coffee?
我把这个叫美国
I call this America.
抱歉,市长,事情发展就到现在这样
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor, that's where we are at this point.
等一下,等一下
Now, hold on, hold on.
你是要告诉我
You're telling me,
在选举的这个月撤离这个城市吗?
that in an election month I evacuated this city for nothing?
你知道疏散市民所付出的代价吗?
Do you realize what this evacuation will cost the people of this city?
我们一直在监测环岛海域
We've been monitoring all the waters around the island.
目前我们还不能认为他已经离开这片地区
As far as we can tell' this thing has not left the area.
是的,但你是不能肯定
Yes. But you don't know for sure.
我们有理由相信他可能藏在一个建筑禁区里
We have reason to believe it may be hiding in a building in the restricted area.
但你是不能肯定
But you don't know for sure!
市长先生!
Mr. Mayor.
我们不能给出安全确定
We cannot give the all-clear,
直到每一个建筑被清查
until each and every building has been checked.
什么事?
What is it?
抱歉,长官
Excuse me, sir.
这可能比我们预计的更加困难
That may be more difficult than we projected.
哦,太好了,太好了
Oh. Terrific. Terrific!
又一个好消息
More good news!
我们碰到的一个问题
We've run into a problem.
你能相信吗?
Do you believe this?
我不知道是怎么回事
I don't know what's going on.
你从来不知道是怎么回事
You never know what's going on.
谢谢
Thank you.
就在这里,长官
Right here, sir.
叫他们下去了
Have them fall in.
我们走,到下面集合
Let's go, people, fall in downstairs.
23号大街地铁站　6号入口
安德森中尉和他的手下今天下午发现了这里
Lieutenant Anderson and his men found this, this afternoon.
我们检查了办公大楼的上层
We were checking the office building above,
发现上面的地板不见了
and we discovered the floor was gone.
当我们发现他会通过打隧道的方式移动时
When we discovered that he could burrow his way through the tunnels realized that...
我们意识到他可能不在这个地区了
we realized he could be outside the quarantine zone.
老天
Holy Christ.
有多少条离岛通道?
How many tunnels lead off the island?
只有14个,长官,我们都查过了
Only 14. Sir. We checked them all.
他一条都没用过
He hasn't used any of them.
把它们都封死
Have them all sealed up.
遵命,长官
Yes, sir.
我们要...怎么做?长官?
How? How would we do that, sir?
把它们填满水泥
Will you fill them with cement,
砌上砖头
brick them up,
布上地雷、炸弹
put landmines in them. and bombs.
我不管什么方法!
I don't care!
确保这该死的东西逃不出这个岛
Make sure the damn thing doesn't leave the island.
遵命,长官
Yes, sir.
其实,他不是什么想要逃跑的敌人
You know, he's not some enemy trying to evade you.
他只是个动物
He's just an animal.
你有什么建议?
What are you suggesting?
在我抓蚯蚓时
Well, when I had to catch earthworms.
我知道最好的办法不是把它们挖出来
I knew the best way to get them was not to dig them out,
而是勾引出来
but to draw them out.
我们只需要了解他需要什么
All we need to do is to find out what he needs,
那他就会来找你
and he'll come to you.
布朗
Brown.
他们在哪?
Where are they now?
三角尺,护航队的位置在哪里?
Delta Niner, where is the convoy position?
指挥官,他们刚进入城市
Command, they've just entered the city.
我们和护航队失去了联系
I have no contact with the convoy.
我希望可以联络到他们
I'm expecting ground confirmation.
长官
Sir,
护航队预计十分钟左右到达,长官
convoy ETA is 10 minutes. Sir.
好的,我们的快点了,我们走
All right. We've got to hurry. Here we go.
全体立刻就位
Man your positions now.
十分钟左右到达
Ten minutes ETA.
行动,行动,行动!所有部门行动
Go, go, go! All systems go.
行吗?
Is it good?
行
Good.
快走,快走!快,让它过去!
Let's go, let's go! Come on, move it through!
拍到照片,可以离开了,让·卢克
We have picture. You can leave, Jean Luc.
我们收到一个信号,长官
We have a signal, sir.
你就说这是法国碳烤咖啡!
You said this was French Roast!
多加点奶
More cream.
带他们进来
Bring them in.
对,快点,把它带回来!
Yea. Come on, bring it back!
我希望这计划能成功
I sure hope this plan of yours works.
我也希望这样
I'm kind of hoping that myself.
你同意这么做吗?
Did you approve this?
他们已经同意了
They just appropriated it.
12辆城市垃圾车
Twelve of the city's dump trucks.
你可以告诉我这是什么回事吗?
Would you like to tell me what's going on here?
事实上不行,我不能说,什么都不要碰
Actually, no, I wouldn't. And don't touch anything.
奥尼尔现在怎么样?
How's O'Neal doing?
一切都在控制中,长官
Everything is on schedule, sir.
你确定你不知道这事吗?
Sure you didn't know about this?
不,没人告诉过我这事
No. No one told me anything about this.
为何我还把你留在身边?
Why do I even keep you around?
卸!
Dump!
这真愚蠢
That's stupid.
不
No.
非常聪明
Very clever.
好了,我们把它堆起来,然后离开这里
All right, let's pile it on, and let's get out of here.
这鱼可真多
That's a lot of fish.
来吧,你个畜生,晚饭时间到了
Come on, you bastard, it's suppertime.
看看那些该死的鱼,这样有用吗?
Look at all that frigging fish. Is this gonna work?
我们得把下水道口打开
We gotta get the manholes uncovered.
我们得让他闻到味道
We want him to smell the bait.
来吧!
Come on.
动作快!动作快!
Let's go! Let's go!
加油,伙计们
Come on, guys.
把盖子打开,快,快,快!
Let's get those lids off. Go, go, go!
他在干什么?
What the hell is he doing?
好了,这边,这边,快
Okay, this way, this way. Come on.
好的,我们上!
Right, Let's go!
快来,在那里!
Come on. Over there!
还有这个
This one.
给我钩子
Give me the crowbar.
在这里就位
Set up here.
我已经瞄准了
I've got a shot.
我是阿尔法6队的查理,我们要前进了
This is Six Alpha Charlie. We gotta move.
我们不能原地不动,我们得继续前进!
We can't stay put, we gotta move!
我们行动,退后
Let's go, fall back!
走,走,走,走!
Go, go, go, go!
我们需要更大的枪
We need bigger guns.
系 统 出 错
我们失去通讯了,长官
We've lost communications. Sir.
快点再连接
Get us back online.
立即开火!
Fire at will!
军士,立即开火!
Sergeant, fire at will!
操,行了,开火!开火!开火!
Fuck, right. Fire! Fire! Fire!
奥尼尔,你最好告诉我发生了什么事情
O'Neal, you better tell me what's going on.
他...他跑了,长官,他跑了,回声...
He's... He's gone, sir, he's gone. Echo...
回声部队在追缉
Echo unit in pursuit.
跟我来
Follow my lead.
所有系统装备完毕,回声4武装
All systems armed. Echo 4 armed.
我们速度有80节,但他要甩开我们了,长官
We're doing 80 knots and he's pulling away, sir.
我锁定目标了
I've got him locked on.
目标锁定,长官,目标被锁定
Locked on, sir. Target is locked on.
发射导弹
Fire the damn missile.
回声1至4号,立即开火
Echo 1 through 4, fire at will.
发射响尾蛇导弹
Fire sidewinders.
哦,该死的,呃...
Oh. Damn! Uh...
这次没有击中,重复,这次没有击中
That is a negative impact. I repeat, that is a negative impact.
没有击中,长官
Negative impact, sir.
没有击中?
"Negative impact"?
那该死的可是克莱斯勒大楼
That's the damn Chrysler Building we're talking about.
告诉我他已经瞄准了
You told me he had it locked on.
回声1号,我们看到你锁定好了
Echo 1, we had you locked on.
那是热追踪式导弹,长官
The heat-seekers can't lock. Sir.
他比他周围这些建筑物还要冷
He's colder than the buildings around him.
弗雷迪
Freddie.
弗雷迪!
Freddie!
干嘛?干嘛?
What? What?
我们快走吧,趁还没被抓
Let's go before we get caught.
吉米,有时候在坏的事情发生之前
Jimmy. You know that bad feeling I get,
你会不会有不祥的预感?
when something really bad is gonna happen?
有啊
Yea.
我现在就有这种感觉,老兄
I'm getting that feeling right now, man.
下降至300英尺,激光制导,系统就绪
Descend to 300 feet. Lasers on. All systens on
目标在11点钟方向
Target, 11 o'clock.
他去哪了?
Where'd he go?
回声小队,靠拢一点,伙计们,准备开火
Echo flight, get it together, guys. Prepare to fire.
回声4号,准备就绪
Echo 4, ready.
回声2号,准备就绪
Echo 2, ready.
开火!
Fire!
我想我们干掉他了
I think we got him.
我们损失了回声1号和2号,长官
We've lost Echo 1 and 2, sir.
该死
Damn
回声4号,目标在哪?
Echo 4, where is target?
哦,天哪!
Oh. Jesus!
他在我的后面,长官
He's right on my tail, sir.
我觉得我甩不掉他了
I don't think I can shake him.
我想我甩掉他了
I think I lost him.
我们...
We've...
我们损失了回声4号,长官
We've lost Echo 4, sir.
你的人是怎么回事?
What's the matter with you people?
你们造成的损失比那该死的东西还要大
You've caused more damage than that goddamn thing did!
好了,来,冷静,吃点糖
All right, Coming here. Calm down. Have some candy.
我不要吃糖,别烦我!
I don't want any candy. Leave me alone!
我...我不敢相信,我意思是...
I... I can't believe it. I mean...
他搞毁了这一切,而...
He did all of this, and...
我们拿他没办法
we did nothing to him.
不,不是这样
No. That's not true.
我们喂了他
We fed him.
在新泽西的指挥中心
Here at the command center in New Jersey.
没有进一步的报导
There is no new information to report.
军方采取了对媒体停止供电的措施
There's the military has clamped a total media blackout on,
不准报道任何事
whatever is going on of it.
官方没有任何有关他们将如何制止或控制这个生物的说明
Officials are not saying anything about their attempts to contain or control this creature.
现在我们看到他们回来了...
And now I cam see they are back form...
好了,情况已经得到了控制
Okey. No, the situation is under control.
事情被控制住了,我们已经遏制了
It's under control, we have containment.
有什么需要帮忙的?年轻人?
Can I help you, young man?
是的,呃...有没有家用的验孕测试剂?
Yes. Uh...Do you have any at-home pregnancy tests?
最好是那些类似于促性腺激素或克罗米芬
Especially ones that look for gonadotropic hormones or clomiphene citrate?
我不知道,这些...
I don't know. This...
这些...
This...
我们有的就这些了
This is all we've got.
我全要了
I'll take all of them.
哇,你大概已经妻妾成群了吧
Wow, you must have quite some harem.
奥黛莉?
Audrey?
哦,天哪,是...
Oh, my God. Is...
奥黛莉,是你吗?你在这里做什么?
Audrey, is that you? What are you doing here?
嗨,你好
Hi. Hello.
哇,多少钱?
Wow. How much is that?
46美元
$46.00
天啊,你...看起来...哇!
God, you... you look... Wow!
你好吗?
How have you been?
见到你很高兴,尼克
It's good to see you, Nick.
你做到了
So you made it.
什么?
What?
你是记者了,嗯?
You're a reporter, huh?
这太好了,太好了,这是你一直以来的愿望
No, that's good. That's good. That's what you always wanted.
我为你高兴
I'm happy for you.
真的,很高兴
Really, I am.
你还生我的气吗?
You're still mad at me?
瞧
Well,
你离开时电话也不留
you left without a phone call,
信也没有,什么都没有
a letter, nothing.
直到现在...是,是的
All this time... Yeah. Yeah,
我猜我还是有点生气
I guess I am still a little mad.
已经八年了
That was eight years ago.
人是会变的
Some people change.
大多数人不会
Most people don't.
那,很抱歉让你这么觉得
Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
奥黛莉
Audrey.
你说得对
You're right.
八年是段很长的时间
Eight years is a long time.
可以请你喝杯茶吗?
Can I make you a cup of tea?
当然,太好了
Sure, that'd be nice.
我还是不明白
I still can't believe it.
我是说,为什么一个反核人士
I mean. How does a guy go from anti-nuke activist...
会为核管理委员会工作?
to working for the Nuclear Regulatory Commission?
在大学里你和我一起游行
When you and I went to rallies together in college,
只是给人们传播意识
we helped to create awareness.
但现在
But now,
作为内部人
from the inside,
我能够实现真正的改变
I'm able to effect real change.
那你想改变出什么样的效果呢?
And. Exactly what changes are you trying to effect?
我在为政府做一个调查
I'm preparing a census for the government.
我正在把因核污染变异
I'm cataloging new species that have been created...
而产生的新物种编排科目
as a direct result of nuclear contamination.
那就是你认为这东西变异的原因?
Is that what you think created this thing?
是的,傍晚的时候我找到了些血液样本
Yeah. I found a blood sample earlier this evening.
你离那东西有多近?
How close did you get to the thing?
非常近
I got pretty close.
那你还发现了什么?
And what else did you find out?
还有,我们知道它要吃成吨的鱼
Well, we know he eats tons of fish.
他是两栖类,他是穴居动物
He's amphibious. He's a burrower.
还有...
And...
他怀孕了
he's pregnant.
他怀孕了?
He is?
他...
He...
他很不寻常
A very unusual he.
我的意思是,显然...
I mean, obviously...
这些测试剂不是为了测验他而设计的
these tests weren't designed for this,
但,基本原理是它们在寻找相同的荷尔蒙结构就表明怀孕了
but fundamentally they look for the same hormonal patterns to indicate pregnancy.
但我不明白
But, I don't get it.
如果他是这个种类的第一个
If he's the first of his kind,
他怎么会怀孕呢?
how can he be pregnant?
他不需要异性吗?
Doesn't he need a mate?
若他是无性繁殖呢?
Not if he reproduces asexually.
这会有什么意义呢?
Where's the fun in that?
我一直在想,他为什么要长途跋涉过来?
I kept thinking', why would he travel so far?
但这么说就合理了
But it makes perfect sense.
很多动物长途跋涉就是为了繁殖
Lots of animals travel great distances for reproduction.
这就是他来纽约的原因,他要筑巢
That's what he's doing in New York. He's nesting.
筑巢?
Nesting?
是的
Yes.
你知道一只蜥蜴一次可下12个以上的蛋吗?
Do you realize that a lizard can lay up to 12 eggs at a time?
想像一下
Think of it.
这我不知道
I didn't know that.
请原谅,我...
Forgive me, I...
我必须去趟实验室,看看能否证实这个理论
I have to get this to the lab and see if I can confirm all this.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
最初目击录像带
最高机密
ゴジラ
Godzilla.
得了,乔伊,这里什么都没有
Come on, Joey' there's nothing down here.
我告诉你,伙计,我听见...
I'm telling you, man, I heard...
有东西
something.
你什么也没听见
You heard nothing.
这是个死胡同
It's a dead end.
有东西吗?
Anything?
不
No.
没什么
Nothing down here.
什么都没有
Nothing at all.
这就是为什么,在这种情况下
This is why, in this case,
国王所有的人马都不能将这座城堡恢复原样
all the king's horses and all the king's men may not be able to put the Big Apple together again.
奥黛莉·提曼兹,WIDF新闻台
Audrey Timmonds, WIDF News.
太棒了!
Yes!
搞定了,你得请我喝啤酒
That's it. You owe me a beer.
这样行吗?
You like it?
行啊
Yeah.
我不该将头发扎到后面
I should've worn my hair back.
不,那样很好
No, it looks great.
你喜欢那样啊,好,好
Are you like it? Good, good.
能问你一个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
嗯,什么?
Yea, what?
你怎么拿到这些东西的?
How did you get ahold of this?
嗯,你瞧
Well, you know.
这就像你说的
It's like you said,
好人最后都没有好报
nice guys finish last.
谢谢,我爱你
Thank you. I love you.
哦,是啊,当然
Oh, yeah, sure.
什么...?
What...?
莫瑞!莫瑞!过来一下
Murray. Murray! Come here a second.
等一下,好吗?什么事?
Hold on a second, all right? What is it?
我有这东西到过其他地方的独家证据
I've got exclusive footage of other places this thing has attacked.
你有吗?
You do?
对
Yeah.
是谁采访的?
Whose story is that?
我
Mine.
军队,警察...
Military, police...
大队人马转移前往那里
There's a lot of movement down there.
怎么啦?
What?
这是我的早餐
It's my breakfast.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
安静!
Quiet!
但,如我们能将他引到更加开阔的区域
But. As if we can lure him into a more open area,
比如中央公园的这个地方
such as this portion of Central Park,
我想就可以制服他
I think we should be able to take him down.
上次你们甚至一点都没伤到他
Last time you didn't even scratch it.
不见得
That's not true.
我们的蚯蚓人,我是说...
My worm guy, I mean...
泰特普勒斯博士已经取到了血样
Dr. Tatopoulos has found blood.
是的,是的,我拿到了
Yes, Yes, I did.
所以,你们看,我们唯一需要做的就是
So. You see, the only thing we need to do...
就是让他到地势开阔的地方
is get him out into open terrain,
使用的武器就不需要依赖于热追踪技术...
and use weapons that don't rely on heat-seeking technology...
呃,抱歉,长官
Uh. Excuse me, sir.
我认为现在的情况开始变得...
I think the situation has become...
更为复杂了
more complicated than that.
我收集到的血样...
The blood I collected...
显示这个生物即将下蛋
revealed that the creature is either about to lay eggs,
或是已经下了
or already has.
是你想告诉我们还有另外更多的这种东西在那里吗?
Are you trying to tell us that there's another of those things out there?
不,不,州长,我不这么认为
No, no, governor, I don't believe so.
等等,等等...
Wait a minute, wait...
但...
But...
他是怎么怀孕的?
Then how can it be pregnant?
他是什么?处女蜥蜴吗?
What is this, the Virgin Lizard?
不,不,这个是无性繁殖
No, no, it reproduces asexually.
所以我们必须尽快找到巢穴的所在
That's why we have to find the nest as soon as possible.
否则将诞生多达十几只
Otherwise up to a dozen will be born,
每一只又会自己下蛋
each one capable of laying eggs on its own.
很快我们就会看到他们的数量会庞大地增加
Very quickly we could be looking at an enormous population.
那么我们先杀死这个生物,然后搜索巢穴
So after we kill the creature, then we search for the nest.
不,我认为这样可能会耽误太久
No, I think it might be too late by then.
这些蛋孵化速度非常快
These eggs are going to hatch very quickly.
你为什么会这么判断呢?
How could you possibly know that?
那些鱼,我们在地铁里发现的鱼
The fish. The fish that we found on the subway.
那不是他为自己储备的食物
He's not collecting all this food just for himself.
他是在为幼崽储备食物
He's preparing to feed his young.
有这个人的新消息吗?
Do we have something on this guy?
有
Yes.
教授兼博士
Doctor and Professor...
尼克...
Nick...
尼克...尼克·塔...塔托...
Nick Ta... Tat... Tato...
他们叫他"蚯蚓人"
They call him "the worm guy."
...敬请期待一次特别报告
Stay tuned for a special report.
喂!
Yo!
哦,对不起,抱歉...
Well, Excuse us, please...
你要去哪?
Where you been?
这个之后就播你的了
Your spot is up right after this.
哦,好的
Oh, good.
能把声音调大点吗?拜托
Could you turn it up, please?
喂
Yo,
能把声音调大点吗?电视音量
Can you turn it up, please? The TV?
如果泰特普勒斯博士说得对
If Dr. Tatopoulos is right,
我们就要在这个问题升级之前迅速采取行动
we have to act quickly before this problem escalates.
你是想基于某些野生动物的理论而分散我们的打击力量吗?
You want to divide our efferts based solely on some wild theory?
长官
Sir,
尼克是我们认可的,如果他强烈的认为...
Nick's come through for us before, and if he feels strongly...
你们认可的?上校,你们的方式是一场灾难
Come through for you? Colonel, your campaign's a disaster.
你竟然无法将这东西赶出曼哈顿
You weren't even able to keep this thing out of Manhattan.
抱歉,先生们,但我认为我们应该看看这个
Excuse me, gentlemen, but I think we should see this.
...了解曼哈顿新来的害虫的行动方式和动机
...Methods and motivations of Manhattan's newest unwanted pest.
ゴジラ
Godzilla.
"酷兹拉"
"God-zilla."
是日本水手传唱的歌谣中出现的词
That's what Japanese sailors called him in song,
是神话中令他们心中充满恐惧的海龙
a mythological sea dragon who filled their hearts with fear.
哦,我的天哪,他偷了我的报导!
Oh, my God! He stole my report!
是的,我知道
Yeah, I know.
这个神话已经成为现实,我们当今的恐怖事件
That myth has become reality, our modern-day terror.
我真不敢相信!
I don't believe it!
这酷兹拉是什么东西?
Who is this Godzilla?
他从哪里来?
Where did he come from?
他为何到这里?
Why is he here?
是念哥斯拉,你个白痴!
And it's "Gojira, you moron!
一条行迹可从曼哈顿追溯到法属波利尼西亚
A direct path can be traced from Manhattan to French Polynesia,
那里的核试验已经持续了二十多年
where nuclear tests have been going on for two decades.
研究员泰特普勒斯博士
Researcher Dr. Tapadopoulos,
认为那只生物正在筑巢
believes the creature may be nesting.
依靠曼哈顿从零开始地进行物种培育
Using Manhattan as ground zero to cultivate the species.
目前,竟然连美国军方的联合打击都可能已无法制服...
This, despite the fact that the combined might of the U.S. Military has been unable to subdue...
是你透露给新闻界的?
You went to the press with this?
没有
No.
没有,我没告诉过任何人
No, I haven't talked to anyone.
他们都提到了你的名字!
They mentioned you by name!
是啊
Yeah.
你给了他们录像带?
You gave them the tape?
不,我没有...我没有没给他们带子
No, I didn't... I didn't give them the tape.
不,带子还在我的帐篷里
No, it's in my tent right now.
哦,天啊
Oh, my God.
噢,天啊,她拿走了
Oh, my God, she took it.
收拾好你的东西,先生
Pack your stuff, mister.
你的研究工作就此结束,立即执行
You're officially off this project, as of now.
这是怎么回事?
What's going on?
我们走
We're leaving.
对这一切我感到很遗憾
I'm so sorry about all this.
一定要让希克斯尽快找到巢穴
Make sure that Hicks finds that nest,
不然就太晚了
before it's too late.
我会尽力的
I'll try.
什么意思,他不在那里?
What do you mean, he's not there?
几秒钟前你还说他在另一条线上
A second ago you said he was on the other line.
拜托,是紧急事情,我真的要和他通话
Please, it's urgent. I really need to talk to him.
没错,尼克·泰特普勒斯
Yes. Nick Tatopoulos.
你要走吗?
You're leaving?
为什么?
Why?
是因为我吗?是因为报道吗?
Is it because of me? Because of the story?
你觉得还会是因为什么?
What did you think would happen?
你没说这是机密档案
You never said it was off the record.
我不需要强调这一点的,奥黛莉
I shouldn't have to, Audrey.
你应该是我的朋友
You were supposed to be my friend.
我信任你的
I trusted you.
尼克,有件事我要告诉你
Nick, there's something I have to tell you.
其实,我对你撒了谎,我不是记者
Look, I lied to you. I'm not a reporter.
我们分手后,我刚来到纽约的时候
When we broke up and I first came out to New York,
我是那么自信我一定会成功
I was so sure I'd make it.
但我没有
But I haven't.
这就是为什么我要这样子抢新闻的原因
That's why I needed the story so bad.
我只是不想告诉你我是个失败者
I just couldn't tell you I'm a failure.
但你觉得这样就可以偷走我的录像带?
And you thought that made it okay to steal my tapes?
不
No.
这么做很糟糕,我真的不该那么做
It was a terrible thing to do. I never should've have done that.
祝你在新职位上一切顺利
Good luck with your new career.
我觉得你能如愿的
I really think you have what it takes.
纽瓦克机场
Newark Airport.
对不起
I'm sorry.
哦,嘿哟!别这样,饶了她吧,行吗?
Oh. Hey, yo! Come on, give her a break, will you?
对不起,这是去机场最近的路吗?
Excuse me, is this the best way to the airport?
先生,你去哪里?
Sir, where are you going?
嘿
Hey,
喂!
hello!
好了,停下
Okay, stop.
把车停下,马上
Stop the car, right now.
行了,让我下车
All right. Now let me out of here.
恐怕我不能这么做
I'm afraid I can't do that.
嘿,我认识你,不是吗?
Hey, I know you, don't I?
没错
Yeah.
没错,你是那个保险公司的
Yeah. You're that insurance guy.
特工菲利普·罗奇
Agent Philippe Roache.
DGAC
法国国家安全局
French National Security Agency.
听起来很吓人
Sounds big.
法国特工
French Secret Service.
我猜你很想知道,你的美国朋友
I thought you'd like to know that your American friends,
已经决定不再找这个生物的巢穴了
have decided not to look for the creature's nest.
什么?你确定?你是如何知道的?
What? Are you sure? How do you know that?
我们知道,相信我
We know. Trust me.
相信你?
Trust you?
你绑架了我,你居然还要我相信你?
You hijack me and you expect me to trust you?
是的
Yes.
我为什么要相信你呢?
And why should I do that?
因为你是唯一一个想找到巢穴...
Because you are the only one who wants to find the nest...
和我一样迫切的人
as much as I do.
你是怎么把这些东西带进我们国家的?
How did you get all this stuff into the country?
这里是美国,我们能买到任何东西
This is America. You can buy anything.
但为何要搞的这么隐秘?
But why all the secrecy?
你们为什么不和美国军方合作?
Why aren't you guys working with the U.S. Military?
我是不能对外说这么多的
I'm not permitted to speak of such things.
嘿,你说的需要我信任你
Hey, you said you needed my trust.
那我也需要你的
Well, then I need yours.
我是一个爱国者
I am a patriot.
我爱我的国家,你能理解的吧?
I love my country. You understand that?
当然
Sure.
我的工作是保卫我的国家
It's my job to protect my country.
甚至有时候我必须保护它本身...
Sometimes I must even protect it from itself.
所犯下的错误
From mistakes we've made.
我们不希望世界知道我们的错误
Mistakes that we don't want the world to know about.
你说的是太平洋上的核试验?
Talking about the nuclear tests in the Pacific?
是的
Yes.
我的国家做了这个试验造成了可怕的后果
This testing done by my country left a terrible mess.
我们来这里...收拾残局
We're here... to clean it up.
他们在8号地点又设置了鱼堆陷阱
They are setting the next fish trap at 8-something.
我们知道如何进入市区
We know how to get into the city'.
只是不知道去哪里开始找
Just don't know where to start look.
这儿
Here.
这里是23号大街地铁站
This is the 23rd Street subway station.
我们最先在这里发现了鱼
That's where we first found the fish.
从这里开始找应该不错
That'd a good place to start looking.
这么说你加入了?
So you're in?
是的
Yeah.
是的,我加入
Yeah, I'm in.
太棒了
Great.
我一直想加入法国外籍军团
I always wanted to join the French Foreign Legion.
- 你好 - 要进去吗?
- Hello. - How's it going?
呃,对不起,对不起,接过,抱歉
Uh. Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon me. Sorry.
哦,亲爱的
Uh. Honey.
嗨,宝贝
Hi, sweetie.
这些都是什么人?
Who the hell are all these people?
怎么啦?我不能让他们睡在大街上
What? I couldn't just let them sleep on the street.
奥黛莉在哪?
Where... Where's Audrey?
在卧室里,因为你在大哭
In the bedroom. Crying her eyes out because of you.
我?我...我做什么了?
Me? What... What did I do?
她的头脑全被你灌输了邪恶的思想
All that "You gotta be vicious" stuff you filled her head with.
我...别胡说!
I fu... Get out of here!
你马上进去和她谈谈
You go in there and talk to her right now.
不是应该你去陪她么,当我没说
Is it being with you? Excuse me.
与某些无聊的报告相反
Contrary to some frivolous reporting.
我们绝对没有任何证据可以去相信...
we have absolutely no information whatsoever to make us believe...
市区里有这个生物的蛋
that there are any eggs of the creature in the city.
没有必要恐慌
There's no need for panic.
重复,没有理由恐慌
Repeat, there's no reason to panic.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
我都做了什么?野兽
What have I done, Animal?
我变成了什么样的人了?
What have I become?
看看我,这不是我,我不会做这种事的
Look at me. This isn't me. I don't do stuff like this.
你是犯了个错误,好吧,已经犯了
You made a mistake. All right? It happens.
是的,瞧
Yeah, well.
我完全害惨了那个唯一会在乎我的人
I just totally screwed up with the only man who will ever care about me.
如果我告诉你你可以去做一些补偿
If I told you, you could make it all up to him.
你会做吗?
Would you?
我当然会
Of course I would.
行了,我们看看这个
All right. Let's get this.
在街上时他离你而去之后
After he left you in the street there,
我就跟着他
I kind of followed him.
我想问他一些感受之类的,你知道吧
I figured I'd talk some sense into the guy. You know.
后来我看到,他被带到一个仓库
Next thing I know, he pulls into this warehouse,
里面全是法国人和各种军事装备
with all these French wackos in military outfits.
他们今晚想尝试潜入市区
They wanna try to sneak back into the city tonight.
他们要去找巢穴
They're going after the nest.
如果他找到了
If he finds it,
我认为就应该是你去让全世界明白
I think you should be the one to let the whole world know,
这家伙是正确的,不是吗?
that he was right all along. Don't you?
那你是要我跟着他潜入市区?
What. You want me to follow him into the city?
对,我们俩都去
Yeah, we both will.
来吧,会很有趣的,会很有趣的,会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun, it'll be fun, it'll be fun.
我不知道...
Well, I dont't know.
我已经把事情搞得一团糟了
I already made a mess of everything.
是啊,你确实搞糟了,奥黛丽
Yeah, you really did, Audrey.
听着,我要去跟踪他了
Listen, I'm going after him.
去不去你自己定,好吗?
You can go with me, or not. Okay?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
不能让露西知道,她会揍我的
Can't let Lucy know. She'll hurt me.
干嘛要嚼口香糖?
What's with the chewing gum?
这样看起来更像美国人
It makes us look more American.
哦,是吗?
Oh, really?
交涉就都由我来吧,好吗?
Just let me do all the talking. All right?
没挂上档
It's not in gear.
跟我来,这边走
Follow me. This way.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
是的,没事
Yea, okay.
快点
Come on.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
这是通往下面地铁隧道的通道
It's a vent that leads down to the subway tunnels underneath.
这里应该可以通往曼哈顿23号大街地铁站
It should take us right to the 23rd Street station in Manhattan.
哦,你一定是在开玩笑吧
Oh. You gotta be kidding me.
这里会不会有老鼠之类的东西?
Aren't there rats and stuff down here?
我更关心有没有蜥蜴
I'm more concerned about lizards.
那令人失望的...
Disappoint,
又大又丑又脏的巨型蜥蜴
Big, ugly, nasty, large lizards.
你们隶属那个部门?
Who are you boys with?
呃,我们是3-2中队的,长官
Uh. We're with the 3-2, sir.
我没问你,小兵
I didn't ask you, soldier.
哦,是...奥尼尔军士
Oh. Well, Sergeant O'Neal...
刚通知我们来的
just called down for us.
要我们马上加入进来,长官,谢谢
He wants us to join him right now. Sir. Thank you.
你不会说话吗?
Have you got a problem talking?
没有,长官,我很好
Why, no, sir. I'm fine.
快点,我们走!
Come on, let's go!
好了,走吧
All right. Keep it moving.
非常感谢
I'll thank you very much.
埃尔维斯·普雷斯利的电影,他是猫王
Elvis Presley movies. He was the king.
长官,奥尼尔的电话
Sir, O'Neal on the line.
奥尼尔,你听得见吗?
O'Neal, do you read me?
听得见,我是奥尼尔
I'll goal for. O'Neal.
我们要怎么做?
How are we doing?
到目前为止,一切都还不错,我们
So far, so good. We're...
我们按计划行事
We're right on schedule.
我们很好,我们...我们很好
We're good. We're... We're good.
噢,天啊
Oh, my God!
是啊
Yeah.
他们在那里,关掉灯,关掉灯
There they are. Kill your light. Kill your light.
哦,拜托,我们怎么下去?我们会跟丢他们的
Oh, Come on, how do we get down there? We're gonna lose them.
他们怎么下去的?
How did they get down there?
不知道
I don't know.
你不觉得他们就是从这里爬下去的?
You don't think they climbed down this thing?
糟糕,哦,上帝!
Whoops. Oh, Jesus!
小心
Careful.
来,拉我一把
Here. Give me your hand.
我来扶你
I got you.
你听见了吗?
Do you hear that?
什么?
What?
野兽,快来!
Animal, come on!
我想我们应该走这边
I guess we go this way.
长官,我们在5号陷阱发现他了
Sir. We've spotted him in section five.
5号...
Section...
准备站斗,快行动,站斗
Combat positions. Here we go! Combat.
目标向北朝着5号陷阱前进,长官
Target's heading north to section five. Sir.
在他离开建筑群进入公园之前不要开火!
Do not fire until he has cleared the buildings and enters the park!
等他进入公园
Wait until he enters the park.
快点
Come on.
他要跑了!该死!开火!立即开火!
He's leaving! Damn it! Fire! Fire at will!
该死!
Damn!
开火!
Fire!
我们采取机动回避飞行!
We'll been Fly to evasive maneuvers.
目标越过障碍朝西部高速路前进
The target is in the clear and headed towards the West Side Highway.
别担心,海军正在那里等着他
Don't worry. The Navy has a little something there waiting for him.
所有单位报告进入战斗状态,长官
All stations report manned for battle station, sir.
好的
Aye.
有序进入,长官
At ordered depth, sir.
好的
Aye.
声纳已经侦测到他了,正在靠近犹他号
We have got him on sonar. Utah closing in.
做最后准备,准备开火
Make final preparations, prepare to fire.
遵命,人工操作准备
Aye, aye, manned and ready.
鱼雷室人工操作已准备,长官
Torpedo room manned and ready. Sir.
确定方位后射击
Final bearing and shoot.
我们锁定了吗?
Are we locked on?
是
Aye.
我们锁定了吗?
Are we locked on?
是的,长官
Aye eye. Sir.
瞄准了,上尉
Locked on, captain.
1号,准备
Number one, stand by.
开火
Fire.
1号鱼雷射离雷管仓
Torpedo one cleared left the tube.
印第安纳号和安克雷奇正号在接近目标
Indiana and Anchorage closing in.
少尉,现在状况如何?
Ensign, what's the status?
我们锁定目标正在接近,长官
We are locked on and closing in, sir.
发射1号鱼雷
Fire number one.
长官,目标正朝我们方向前进
Sir! The target's heading right at us!
全速后退!
All back full!
遵命,长官,全速后退
Aye, aye, sir. All back full.
准备撞击,还有10秒
Stand by for impact. In 10 seconds.
6...
Six,
5...
five,
4...
four...
3...
three,
2...
two,
我们损失了安克雷奇号,长官
We've lost the Anchorage, sir.
他正前转移,长官,他回头往曼哈顿去了
He's shifted course, sir. He's headed back towards Manhattan.
全速前进,锁定追赶
Full ahead. Close in, lock on.
准备3号、4号鱼雷,瞄准
Prepare tubes three and four, lock on.
遵命,长官
Aye, aye, sir.
准备,3号,发射!
Stand by, three. Fire.
3号鱼雷射离雷管仓
Torpedo three cleared and left the tube.
8秒后击中
Impact in eight seconds.
7...
Seven,
6...
six...
3...
Three,
2...
two,
直接命中!
Direct hit!
干掉他了
Got him.
恭喜,长官
Congratulations, sir.
干得好
Good job.
是啊,干得漂亮
Yeah, well done.
那上面是什么?
What's up there?
麦迪逊 花园广场
这味道真不错
This is a good smell.
哦,哇,奥黛丽,看看这里
Oh, wow. Audrey, look at this.
他捣毁了花园
He trashed the Garden.
哦,天啊!我现在很生气
Oh, man! Now I'm pissed.
那是他们的吗?
Is that them?
对
Yeah.
三个蛋
Three eggs.
我还以为会更多
I thought there'd be more.
你说得对
And you were right.
哦,天啊
Oh, my.
这边至少有20个蛋
There's gotta be more than 20 eggs here.
哦,还有更多
Oh. Way more.
危险
高压电
开始数吧
Start counting.
能帮我一下吗?
Could you help me?
好,你还行吗?
Yeah, you all right?
还好
Yep.
好了
There.
我们没有足够的炸药
We don't have enough explosives.
他们到底在干什么?
What the hell are they doing?
尼克,我们出了个问题
Nick, we have a problem.
我的天啊!
My God!
天哪!
God!
快点!我们走!
Come on. Let's go!
等一下,行吗?就一会
One second, all right? One second.
这真是...令人难以置信
This is... unbelievable.
你不觉得我们掌握的证据够了吗?
Don't you think we have enough already?
我只想...
I just want...
是的,我很满足了,很丰富了
Yeah, that's good for me. That's plenty.
我们应该...
We should...
这个...
That's...
不要让它们...
Just let's not...
受到惊吓
startle it.
我们闻起来像鱼
We smell like the fish.
我认为我们现在该离开了
I think we should leave now.
我觉得这是一个好主意
I think that's a good idea.
快!
Come on!
所有人快出去!马上!
Everybody outside! Now!
快,我们走
Come on. Let's go.
跑!
Go!
把门锁上,我们必须把它们困在里面
Lock the doors now! We have to keep them contained inside.
快点,我们走!
Come on. Let's go!
你看到了吗?
You see that?
好了,数到三
All right. On three.
好
Okey.
三!
Three!
这里是尼克斯队洗澡和休息的地方
This is where the Knicks get showered and everything.
天哪
God.
太好了,现在我们该怎么办?
Great. Now what do we do?
我现在站在新泽西进入林肯隧道的入口处
I'm standing just outside the Jersey entrance to the Lincoln Tunnel.
成千上万愤怒的避难者要求回到市区
For a thousands of angry refugees are demanding to be let back into the city.
所有通向市区的主要道路
All major arteries into the city...
都因在曼哈顿的人为制服了哥斯拉欢欣鼓舞而堵塞
are clogged with Manhattanites who are jubilant that Godzilla.
是的,是的,我明白的
Yes, yes, I understand.
你办公室的电话响个不停
Your office is swamped with calls.
我知道,我知道
I know, I know!
你知道外面发生了什么事吗?
Do you have any idea what's going on out there?
我的电话响个不停
The phones are ringing off the hook.
人们大叫着要求回到市区
Will people are screaming to be let back in the city.
我们正在派潜水员潜入河中寻找尸体
We're sending divers into the river now to reach the body.
那东西已经死了,你还在等什么?
That thing's dead. What are you waiting for?
上校
Colonel.
上校,我们必须开始寻找巢穴
Colonel, we've gotta start a search for the nest.
埃尔希,我们已经讨论过这件事了
Elsie, We've been through this already.
如果尼克是对的,我们就不对这件事负责吗?
What if Nick is right, and we blow this whole thing?
长官,这是我们彻底解决这次件事的唯一机会了
Sir. This could be the only chance we have to do something about it.
上尉
Captain,
组织个搜寻派对
organize a search party.
我要对整个城市和地铁进行一次完全的清扫
I want a complete sweep of the entire city and the subway.
你没有权利这么做
You don't have the authority to do that.
阻止我试试
Try and stop me.
联系军事部
Contact the military.
让他们派轰炸机炸毁这座大楼
And get them to send a bomber to blow up this building.
我该怎么做?
How do I do that?
555-7600
555-7600.
告诉他们密码是"蜻蜓"
Tell them it's a Code Dragonfly.
他们就会帮你接通
That should get you through.
你还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
555之后呢?
555 what?
76...00
76... 00
占线中
It's busy.
再试一次
Try again.
他们怎么说?
What did they say?
我不能拨通
I can't get through.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what's wrong.
我们把守上面一层的门
We secured the doors on the upper levels.
让·菲利普和让·皮埃尔在哪里?
Where are Jean-Philippe and Jean-Pierre?
他们没逃出来
They didn't make it.
尼克,我和我的人在这儿挡住它们
Nick, my men and I will hold them here.
你必须出去求救
You'll have to go and get help.
你认为上面能支撑住我们吗?
You think we could fit up in there?
只有这个办法了,不是吗?
There's one way to find out. Right?
是啊
Yea.
把我托起来
Boost me up.
来
Come on.
噢,情况不妙
Oh. This is not good.
情况不妙
This is not good.
快啊,快啊
Come on, come on.
快
Come on.
走错楼层了
Wrong floor.
我们为什么不走这条路呢?
Why don't we go this way?
是我,是我
It's me. It's me.
怎么了?
What happened?
它们松松散散,这个地方到处都是
They're loose. They're all over the place.
我无法出去,没人出得去
I couldn't get out. No one can get out.
你是谁?
Who the hell are you?
奥黛莉?
Audrey?
来
Here.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
我想没事
I think so.
嘿!
Hey!
不准摄影
No cameras.
你这个...?
What are you kid...?
行,好吧,这样很好
Yeah, all right. Very good.
你们有没有对讲机或是手提电话之类的?
Do you have a radio or walkie-talkie?
任何能联络外界的东西?
Anything to contact the outside?
电话试过没?
What about the phones?
没,不好用,线路都短路了
No. It's no good. The circuits are all jammed.
哦,等等
Oh. Wait.
我有个办法
I know a way,
可以让我们发出消息到外面
and how we can get a message to the outside.
这边,快来
This way. Come on.
录像带,录像带!
The tape. The tape!
快!
Come on!
快点
Come on.
快来,广播室就在那边
Come on. The broadcast booth is over here.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know that?
我们在这覆盖了网点播出流浪者队比赛
Our network covers the Ranger games.
锁上的
It's locked.
等等,有密码,有密码
Wait. There's a code. There's a code.
哦,快啊,快啊!
Oh. Come on. Come on!
我差一点就成功了
I was just about to get it.
网点是连接互联网的
The network's on an intranet.
可以直接访问我们的电脑系统
It's a direct feed to our computer system.
你用广播站搜索不会比我出去更容易找到军方的
Your station won't have any easier time reaching the military than I did.
你为他们工作的时候,他们有没有监视所有的...
When you worked with them, did they monitor all the...
新闻广播?
news broadcasts?
是的
Yeah.
是的,他们有
Yeah, they did.
好吧,我们现场直播,嗯?奥黛丽
All right, we'll go live. Uh, Audrey?
我们就在这里报道
We'll broadcast right from in here.
希望他们能看到
Hopefully they'll see it.
我会尽力把消息传出去的
I'll try to get a message through.
让我们不要忘记当我们匆匆返回到市区的时候
Let's not forget in our rush to return to the city that...
很多人的生活已经被永远的改变
many people have had their lives changed forever.
在这个城市里没人不会愤怒...
No one in the city has been untouched by the frenzy...
疾病患者,流离失所者,伤者...
The sick, the displaced, the injured...
都需要我们的帮助
all need our help.
艾迪 @ WIDF转播车 转入CFX1信号频道发送影像!
今晚没流浪者队的比赛啊
There's no Ranger game on tonight.
艾迪,你若看得到
Ed, if you're seeing this,
能把我们送上直播吗?
will you please put us on live?
情况紧急
It's urgent!
我知道这听起来很疯狂,艾迪
I know this sounds crazy, Ed,
但拜托你必须这么做
but please. You have to do it.
拜托,请相信我
Please, just trust me.
我才不会给你直播呢
I'm not putting you on live.
我不认为他会这么做
I don't think he's gonna do it.
哦,会的,他会的
Oh, Yes, he will.
行了,艾迪,快点,嗯?
All right, Ed? Come on. Hum?
看到了吗?艾迪
You see that, Ed?
如果不消灭它们,它们会毁掉这个诚市的
They're gonna be all over the city if we don't stop them.
给我点时间,行吗?
Give me a second, will you?
终于是返回家园的时候了,然后...
Finally it's time to return home, them...
准备好潜水艇
Get the diving boats ready.
好的
Okey.
我们的恐慌也平息了
Our fears have been allayed,
感谢我们穿着制服的男孩们的英勇努力
thanks to the heroic efforts of our boys in uniform.
怎么回事,我们上电视了吗?
What's going on. Are we on?
是的,不错,你上电视了
Yeah, good, you're on.
- 现场直播吗? - 是的,是的
- Are we live? - Yes, yes.
你在电视上了,开始!
You're on. Go!
我们在麦迪逊广场花园做现场报道
We're live inside Madison Square Garden,
这里是尼克·泰特普勒斯博士发现的野兽藏身处
where Niko Dr. Tatopoulos has discovered the beast's lair.
博士,您能告诉我们这里发生了什么吗?
Doctor, can you please tell us what's happening here?
到你了,对,上,上
That's you. Yes, go, go.
谢谢
Thank you.
好,呃...
Yeah. Uh...
那么,我们已经发现了超过200个蛋
Well, we've discovered over 200 eggs.
去找希克斯,找希克斯!
Go get Hicks. Get Hicks!
已经在一阵子前开始孵化
which, a few moments ago, began hatching.
这种生物虽然刚孵化,但身高超过9英尺
The creatures, though just hatched, are over 9 feet tall,
他们已经开始进食
and they've begun feeding.
当他们这里的食物供给耗尽
When their food supply runs out here,
它们将试图自己的猎捕食物
they will attempt to hunt down food of their own,
闯出这个巢穴
outside of this nest.
哦,我的上帝
Oh, my God.
如果它们出去,就会大量繁殖
If they get out, they'll multiply,
很快,一个新的物种将会出现
and very soon a new species will emerge.
一个可以在这个星球上替代我们的优秀物种
One that could replace us as the dominant species of this planet.
这些惊人的爬行动物每个在出生时就怀孕了
Each one of these amazing reptiles are born pregnant.
适应力高又狡猾
Adaptive and cunning,
从两百只繁殖到四万只...
these 200 could become 40,000...
只需要一年
within this year.
如果军方听到这个广播
If the military is listening to this broadcast,
他们应该立即摧毁这幢大楼
they have to destroy this building immediately...
赶在这些生物跑出来之前
before these creatures can escape.
目前为止,它们都还被困在这栋楼里,但...
So far, they're all trapped inside this building, but...
我认为我们无法坚持太久了
I don't think we can contain them for long.
它们很强壮
They're very strong,
很灵巧
they're agile,
还有...
and...
它们正在找食物
they're looking for food.
所以我想您对这个生物筑巢的理论分析是正确的
So I guess your theory of the creature nesting turned out to be correct after all.
不论我们会怎样
Regardless of what happens to us,
最重要的是这栋大楼必须得立即摧毁
the most important thing is that this building be destroyed immediately...
在它们会跑出来窜入城市之前
before they can escape into the city.
我们在麦迪逊广场花园现场报导
Reporting live from Madison Square Garden.
我是奥黛莉·提曼兹,WIDF新闻台
This is Audrey Timmonds' for WIDF News.
谢谢,奥黛莉
Thanks, Audrey.
不客气
Sure.
这就是命令,要我把每个字拼出来吗?
That's affirmative. Let me spell it out for you.
我要你们炸了麦迪逊广场花园
I want you to blow up Madison Square Garden.
你们成功了
军方说你们
只有六分钟逃出
否则会被烤焦
快逃出去!!!!!
瞧,好消息是他们收到了信息
Well, the good news is they got that message.
坏消息是我们只有六分钟...
The bad news is we've got less than six minutes...
可以逃出这幢大楼
to get out of the building.
好了,派对结束,该离场了
Okay. the party's over, Time to leave.
有人和我一起吗?
Anyone care to join me?
你在哪里找到这个人的?
Where did you find this guy?
他是法国人
He's from France.
骏马1-5,IP植入
Stallion 1-5 is IP inbound.
你没事吗?
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
伙计们,伙计们,这边走,快
Guys, guys, this way. Come on.
哦,天啊,那些鱼!
Oh, my God. The fish!
尼克,快!
Nick, come on!
它们吃完了所有的鱼
They've eaten all the fish.
快点,尼克,这边
Come on, Nick, this way.
这边不行,回那边去!
Not this way, back that way!
扶手电梯!
The escalators!
快点!
Hurry!
骏马,检查主武器
Stallions, check master arms on.
...2...3
Two, three.
我想我甩掉它们了
I think I lost them.
骏马1-5,我们在花园楼顶用激光制导
Stallion 1-5 showing a good laser track on top of the Garden.
选用大型对地制导炸弹
Selecting LGB.
我们还剩多少时间?
How much time do we have left?
不到30秒
Less than 30 seconds.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
跑!快跑!
Go! Let's go!
我们走!快点!
Let's go, come on!
快!快!
Come on! Come on!
送出小野牛
Send your Mavericks.
两枚
Two away.
制导准确命中
Lead has good hits.
你没事吗?
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
我从来没想到过你的人生会是如此刺激
Somehow I never thought your life was this exciting.
你会大吃一惊的
You'd be surprised.
我想探寻一下
I'd like to find out.
你怎么样?你没事吧?
How are you doing? You all right?
我喝杯咖啡就好了
I could use a coffee.
他看上去很愤怒
He looks angry.
我们...我们...我们...我们怎么办?
What... What... What... What do we do?
逃跑是个很好的注意
Running would be a good idea.
快跑!
Let's go!
快!快!
Come on. Come on!
进去,进去
Get in, get in.
进去!
Get in!
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
呃...你最好快点,法国先生
Uh... You better step on it, Mr. French.
从57号大街穿过城区进入西部高速路
Take 57th across town and cut up the West Side.
不,你疯了?沿罗斯福大道走
No, are you crazy? Take... take the FDR.
别闹了!下雨走罗斯福大道?
Please! The FDR, in the rain?
应该有张地图的
There ought to be a map.
他越来越大了
It's getting larger.
去走西部高速路
Take the Westside Highway.
我找到个东西
I got one.
不,不,不,西部高速路还在修
No, no, no, the West... the West Side's got construction.
这是地铁图!
This is a subway map!
百老汇街呢?
Broadway?
不,不,不,不
No, no, no, no.
快点决定!
Make up your minds!
百老汇!走百老汇街!
Broadway! Take Broadway!
快点!
Come on!
确认,我们沿百老汇街然后...
Affirmative. We're traveling down Broadway and...
在34号大街右转
Make... make a right on 34th Street.
那是奥尼尔!
That was O'Neal!
大家都好吗?大家都没事吧?
Is everybody okay? Is everybody all right?
调头
Turn around.
什么?
What?
快点!
Do it!
不
No.
什么?为什么?
What? Why?
指挥中心,回话
Command Center, come in.
指挥中心,我是奥尼尔
Command, this is O'Neal.
奥尼尔!
O'Neal!
奥尼尔,怎么回事?
O'Neal, what's going on?
他回来了,长官
He's back, sir.
他回来了
He's back.
哥斯拉仍然活着!
Godzilla is still alive.
罗杰斯中尉,那些F-18还在空中吗?
Lieutenant Rodgers, are those F-18's still in the air?
是的,长官,他们正在回基地的路上
Yes, sir. They're heading back to base.
叫他们回来
Turn them around.
在这里,在这里
Here it is. Here it is.
长官,我们在找什么?
Sir, what are we looking for?
每个出租车公司都有装配无线电
Every cab company keeps a record...
在每一辆出租车上
of each of its cabs, radio frequencies.
找到了
Bingo.
嘿嘿,他越来越近了
Hey. Hey. He's getting closer.
那里,那里!隧道!走隧道
There, there! The tunnel! Go in the tunnel.
前面已经被堵死了
They've got it blocked off.
现在你觉得去哪儿好?
Now where would you like to go?
把灯关掉
Turn off the lights.
尼克,你在吗?
Nick, are you there?
尼克?
Nick?
奥尼尔?奥尼尔?奥尼尔?
O'Neal? O'Neal? O'Neal?
用车辆编号这招真聪明,你在哪里?
Nice trick with the cab ID. Where the hell are you?
你一定要帮我们,我们在...
You have to help us. We're in the...
公园大道隧道
Park Avenue Tunnel.
他想要钻进来
He's gonna traveled in here.
好了,尼克,听我说
Ok, NIck. Listen to me.
你们必须要把他引到开阔的地方
You guys have got to low him out of into the open area.
这样我们可以明确的向他攻击,完毕
So we can get a clear shot at him. Over.
没问题,需要我们把他洗洗干净吗?
No problem. You want us to wash him up for you too?
最近的吊桥是哪座?
Where's the nearest suspension bridge?
呃...布鲁克林,布鲁克林
Uh... Brooklyn. Brooklyn.
我们走
Let's go.
那你觉得我们该怎么出去?
And how would you like us to do that?
这玩意有没有远光灯?
Does this thing have high beams?
开灯!
Now!
长官,他正在向布鲁克林大桥前进
Sir, he's headed toward the Brooklyn Bridge.
目标正向布鲁克林大桥前进,长官
Target is heading toward the Brooklyn Bridge. Sir.
让F-18直接前往布鲁克林大桥
Direct the F-18's to the Brooklyn Bridge.
布 鲁 克 林 大 桥
曼  哈  顿  出  口
他没有跟着我们
He's not following us.
是吗?
Really?
噢,天啊!
Oh, my God!
你不是在跟我开玩笑吧,老兄?
Will you gotta be kidding me, man?
我们在他嘴里!
We're in his mouth!
你走错路了,老兄
You're going the wrong way, man.
你走错路了
You're going the wrong way.
这会你能闭嘴吗?
Will you shut up, now?
好了,出去!出去!
Okay, gun it! Gun it!
走,走,走!出去!
Go, go, go! Gun it!
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
快点!快点!快点!
Move it, move it, move it!
奥尼尔
O'Neal!
奥尼尔,我们做到了
O'Neal, it worked!
他被电缆缠住
He's caught in the suspension cables.
攻击吧!马上!
Do it! Now!
收到
Roger that.
骏马1-5,目标在桥上
Stallion 1-5, tally one on the bridge.
锁定后开始攻击
Lock on and fire at will.
发射两枚
Two away.
直接命中,但目标仍在移动,长官
Direct hit, but the target is still moving, sir.
那就调头回来继续攻击!
Well, circle around and fire again!
击败哥斯拉!
那是我丈夫!
That's my husband!
哦,我的上帝
Oh, my...
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
噢,天哪
Oh, my.
哦,上帝
Oh, God.
哦,不
Oh, no.
等等
Wait.
我们可以利用这个机会
We can use this.
市长消灭了哥斯拉
"The mayor who destroyed Godzilla."
我不认为我们应该利用这个
I don't think we should exploit this.
这可能会适得其反
It could backfire.
听我说,白痴
Listen to me, idiot.
是我在这里做的决策
I do the thinking here.
这是一个伟大的决策
It's a magnificent idea.
你想知道我对你和你参加竞选的看法吗?
You know what I think about you and your campaign?
吉英,等等,你要去哪?我需要你
Gene, wait minute. where you going? I need you.
奥尼尔,你听得见吗?
O'Neal, do you read me?
听...听...听...听见了,长官
Yea... Yes, sir.
干的非常漂亮,大兵
That's one hell of a job, soldier.
干的非常漂亮
That's one hell of a job.
收到,长官
Roger that, sir.
我很抱歉,老兄
I'm Sorry, folks.
我已经答应将我的经历作为...
I've already promised my story as...
作为独家报道给...
as an exclusive to...
另一位记者
another reporter.
我们成功了
We did it!
我们成功了,我们拿到独家报道了!
We did it! We got the exclusive!
奥黛莉,你很漂亮
Audrey, you're beautiful.
我们?我不这么认为
We did? I don't think so.
记住,你是为我工作的,好吗?
Just remember, you work for me. Ok?
不再是了,垃圾
Not anymore, Chuck.
我不干了
I quit.
但你...你...
But you... you...
她不干了
She quits.
奥黛莉,奥黛莉
Audrey. Audrey.
摄影机里的录像带你拿出来了吗?
Did you take the tape back from the camera?
没有
No.
我是说,我不会...
I mean, I cant't...
不会弄丢的
couldn't have just lost it.
菲利普在哪?
Where's Philippe?
喂?
Hello?
是我,菲利普
It's Philippe.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
告诉你的朋友,我会把录像带...
Tell you friends. I'll send the tape...
洗掉一些内容后再寄还给他
after I've removed a few items from it.
我明白
I understand.
我要说再见了,还有...
I just wanted to say au revoir. And...
谢谢你们的帮助,我的朋友
Thank you for your help, my friend.
等等...呃...
Well, wait... Uh...
喂?
Hello?
再见
Au revoir.
那个法国人是干什么的?
Who was that French guy anyway?
啊...
Ah...
只是个保险经纪人
Just some insurance guy.
他是不是...他是不是说拿了我的录像带?
Did he take my...? Did he say anything about my tape?
是的,他说他拿了你什么录像带之类的
Yeah, he said something about your tape.
他拿了我的录像带?
Does he have my tape?
是的,他拿了你的录像带
Yeah, he has your tape.
他怎么拿的这么快?
How he fet so fast?
他会寄还给你的
You'll get it back.